I'm talking about the fact that he was actually a stay dog.
It's sad.
It's awful.
Hey, hey, hey.
This is good for me.
It's getting through to me.
Sleepy. Sleepy.
It's 9:00 a.m., but it was earlier.
It's been a rough day. It's been a while.
It was so early in the morning.
Yesterday it was raining heavily,
But today is very warm in Saharz.
It sure is.
It's great.
Yes, it's great.
Cut!
Yes, we need to go around a little bit more!
Yes, cut!
It's aye-aye, sir.
It's windy.
They're running head-on.
Yes, sir.
I've only been able to take a corner once in 10 years, but I have it now.
That's why it hurts so much to run while eating bread.
Dash! Pass him!
Okay, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Thank you for watching.
I knew I shouldn't have.
It looks so good and smells so good.
I think I'm going to tear it off.
I think it's going to get torn off.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No matter how soft I bite it...
Blah, blah, blah...
I can smell it in my nose.
It smells so good!
I ate it.
Can I eat it now?
Bon appétit!
Boom, boom!
Cut!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Dog! Dog! Dog! Dog!
Dog!
Aah!
Hello!
Where's Dog?
Dog!
Sankosha!
Yes, Cut!
Cut!
I love it!
That's a cat!
Cat!
I love it!
Yes, cut!
Cut!
OK!
Cat!
Yes, OK.
Yes, cut!
OK!
Yes, start!
Yes, cut!
OK, perfect!
Cut!
Idiot!
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
Yes, cut!
OK!
Thank you very much!
No, it was very windy!
But the atmosphere outside is over now?
Is it?
It's cold, thank goodness!
It's still kind of harsh!
Today is the day, the weather is nice and warm!
I mean me, warm!
I thought I'd eat comfort food, but I eat so much comfort food!
I thought so!
It's cold!
But the fried chicken was so good!
The eggs were delicious!The eggs were delicious!
Really, they were delicious!
Thank you for the food!
Yes, thank you!
Straight to the throat!
Okay, here we go!
Yeah, yeah!
Hey, hey, are you smiling?
It's smiling!
It's going to a point!
Hey, hey, are you laughing?
It's laughing!
Shut up!
You're so cute! Cute!
Cute!
Doggy, doggy, doggy, doggy in a swaddle!
It was a very strange scene of manipulation!
Let's start!
Okay, I'll try to shoot while accelerating.
Yes, I'm going to shoot!
Okay, I'll start filming!
Yes, please look forward!
Okay, here we go!
Yes, peace!
Yes, OK.
Shall we take a picture too?
You're cute. It's OK.
It's good.
It's cute.
All right.
Thank you for your time.
Yes, OK!
Real perfect!
Huh, it's another beautiful morning.
Awesome.
Good morning.
Morning.
I'm going to lose the phone.
The train hangs up in the morning.
Why?
You have a loud voice.
You have a loud voice, don't you?
How are you?
I'm fine.
OK, cut!
OK, OK!
Cut! Perfect!
Okay, this cut is OK.
All right, let's get started!
You told me to wake you up at 6:30!
You couldn't do it.
You woke me up so much.
Why didn't you wake me?
I didn't know.
I don't know anymore!
Wait a minute.
You forgot to comment.
What happened?
Tough.
Tight.
Cut! It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Yes, ok. It is ok.
Senglas VOCALiman
Evans
Yes, cut!
Yes, thank you!
OK!
Yes, then, yes,
Thank you very much!
That's good.
Looking good.
Start.
Summa.
Yes, OK.
It's great!
Milly.
Yes, okYes, ok.
Yes, okay.
Okay, Millie.
I'm afraid this is my grandmother's.
You can trust me later.
It's the smallest face in the room.
Yes, the dog is twilight.
Yes, I'm coming in.
Dog.
Grandma
Grandma.
Yes, go!
Boom!
Whoa!
Dog! Dog!
You're so cute!
You ran in the river! Where have you been!
You were so cute!
I'm so happy for you!
Are we done with this outfit?
The end!
Thank you for all your hard work!
But it's been so long!
Not yet!
There are more dance scenes to come.
What? It's getting less!
I'll do my best!
It's so cold!
I don't care which one.
Oh, okay?
Just one?
It's so dark!
Look! The sisters of Maron.
Sisters!
They're definitely sisters!
It's a girl, Maron.
So cute!
You have the same face, Maron.
Right?
Yes, ma'am.
Make a sorry face!
Yes, sir.
Smile note
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir.
Then, note a smile.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Give me your head.
I know how to stick my neck out!
So cute!
Look at this.
I could take five of these home with me and they wouldn't even know.
Look at him! He's so cute!
Look at his ears!
Oh! I see them!
He's so cute. He's so cute.
This one's cute, too.
He's so cute.
Lulu Lulu.
Lulu Lulu
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
This is going to be nice and backwards.
Okay, everybody watch the camera.
I love you.
I love you more than anyone.
I wonder if it would be good to have you put out as a profit maker for this.
Did you dance about 30 times?
After about three and a half hours, I started dancing,
It's a mental battle to get to this point.
But I kept my concentration for more than 3 hours.
I made a mistake with Doremi Force.
I only did it about three times.
I made the mistake of doing just the chorus three times.
Sorry.
I said so much. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I will continue to support you.
Please support me.
Please support me.Please support us.
Cheer for them.
The girls are catching up. It's called a growth spurt.
Please give me your best regards.
Yes, that's good.
OK! Spicy!
Yes, cut! Good!
Well, here we go.
What's that?
Be careful.
Yes, yes.
Okay, so, 7chan, that's it for today. Thank you very much.
It was a fun and delicious shoot at the end.
This was one of the longest shoots I've had in a long time, but it was a lot of fun.
Passing fingers.
Finger of pass.
Please make sure you do this part well. Ballet.
Is it here? Not here?
I did it here.
You did it here?
Good luck.
Good luck with the ballet.
Here? It was here?
Here.
It was here.
I'll do my best.
Start!
Cut!
OK!
Okay, Mirika, please leave it like this.
Here we go!
Yes, cut!
Let's go! What are we going to do now? What's this?
Toss!
It's a knee cushion.
Toss.
You do it like this.
Oh!
That's it! That's it!
That's the one!
Excuse me! Careful! Barrel of skin
I have an otaku!
I've been taught otakuri and I'd like to do some real tossing!
I'll do my best!
Thank you for your hard work!
Yes, OK!
OK!
Well then, this test is over for Kanazuka-chan!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Yay!
Well, I'll finish up.
Thank you very much!
Can I eat this too?
Bon appétit!
Good night.